here are the stories were covering this
hanc narrationem hic tegebant
week in the category 5 TV newsroom a
V in hebdomadam genus a TV newsroom
hard drive has been stolen from an
ferreus coegi est susceperat furto ablata est
exclusive club containing the personal
quibus personalis clava exclusive ad
details of members such as Stephen Fry
Details of sodales ut Stephanus Fry
and Lord Rees the US government is
US regimen Domini est quod florenorum
funding mind-control chip research
mentis imperium, investigationis sumptu chip
getting a drone for Christmas if you're
Si vestri 'questus Christi ad fucum
in the UK you may have to consider new
in the UK considerans te vivens ut habeant ad novum
legislation coming this spring
hoc vere leges venire
Uber's driver and customer data has been
Uber et mos est scriptor coegi data fuerit
compromised and they've paid hackers to
et mutaui periculo exponi iudicatur hackers
try and cover it up an Skype has been
experimentum autem eius et operiat illum et fuit Cras
removed from app stores in China these
remota sunt ex Sinis in app stores
stories are coming right up don't go
ecce venient in fabulis iustum non
anywhere
huc
Jeff Weston gentlemen you're building a
Jeff Weston 'o viri ad vos aedificationem
brand-new beautiful website what aren't
novi quod pulchra website notam-sunt
you you're a terrible actor
tu es Actor bellator
what does where acting comes into play I
Quid actum est, ubi ludere in me
don't know you're supposed to act okay
Nescio vos erant 'supponitur ad bene agendum
I'm building a really cool website are
EGO sum aedificium edificium a website sunt realiter refrigerant
you building a really cool website just
building a vere frigus vestri website iustus
because Jeff is confused doesn't mean
Jeff confusa est quoniam non est medium
you have to be visit cap five dot TV
habes quinque dat esse visita cap TV
slash dream host to sign up for
Suspendisse in somnio exercitus preliari
unlimited web hosting for your website
illimitata web hosting pro website
with unlimited email accounts MySQL
cum illimitata MySQL email rationum
databases the latest version of PHP
a tardus version of databases PHP
WordPress and more and even a free
WordPress et magis libera
domain name registration it's less than
adnotatione est minus quam domain nomen
six dollars per month so sign up today
sex pupa per mensis usque hodie ut sign
cat five dot TV / dream host this
cat quinque dat TV / exercitum Hoc Somnium
is the category 5 TV newsroom covering
V TV newsroom genus est operimentum perditioni
the week's top tech stories with a
una sabbatorum historiarum scriptor summo cum tech
slight linux bias I'm Sacha recommended
Linux leve pondus commendatur Sacha sum
here are the top stories were following
hic summo fabulas secuti
this week members of an exclusive club
Haec est exclusive clava membra sabbati
that is restricted to selected graduates
graduati intra id lectus
of Oxford and Cambridge universities are
et universities Oxonie Cambridge sunt
being warned that computer data
quod admonuit, ut computatrum notitia
containing their personal details is
quibus singula eorum propria est:
feared stolen the club believes that a
qui credit in clava et timuerunt me exigebas
backup hard drive has been taken from a
ferreus coegi tergum capta est a
locked room inside its London
London interius cubiculum clausa suo
headquarters the information stored on
super sedes repostum indicium
it is said to include names home
ut dicitur in domum include Nomina
addresses phone numbers and some bank
phone numerus et oratio ripae
details the 5,000 members including
5,000 details inter membra
celebrities such as Stephen Fry have
ut Stephanus Fry in Celebrities
been there have been affected both the
et non esse affectus sunt
police and the members have been
ac magistratus fuerunt membra
notified and private investigators hired
conduxerunt priuataque nota inquisitores
although the Duke of n borough and
Et tamen dux n burgo
Prince of Wales are honorary members of
Filius regis Angliae honorarium sint membra
the club data about them has not been
notitia de his non fui in clava
exposed according to the Telegraph
patere secundum adipiscing
however it did add that Lord Reese one
adde, quod Dominus non fecit tamen unus Reese
of the country's leading astrophysicists
ducit in regionem suam de astrophysicists
is among those thought to be affected
quod cogitavi ut affectus inter eos
the UK's Information Commissioner's
legatus in the UK scriptor Information
Office says that companies need to
Dicit quod officium est opus societates
protect their patrons data in suggesting
patronatus suggerente tueri indicia
the use of encryption as well as
tum usum encryption
ensuring that quality doors and locks
cursus et qualis, et seras,
are used Wow so like an actual situation
Wow sunt et in ipsa rei simile
where information has actually like like
qua notitia ut est vere amo
the hard copy has been stolen oh yeah we
O dura in exemplum furtum non yeah
have this happen in a Canadian
Hoc contingere Canadiensis
government office remember that oh yeah
imperium officii memores, ut venias yeah
three years back when I think it was
tribus annis retro, cum cogito me erat
like like Social Insurance numbers and
ut sicut Social Security et numero
everything yeah if I recall correctly
yeah bene omnia si rite audita recordor
was like potentially an Interpol type
sicut erat in potentia ad Interpol genus
thing Oh hanging out with a girl other
O aliquid aliud tentorium cum puella
country oh wow well there but it's just
o patria wow non bene, sed suus 'iustus
a hard drive full of data so here you
ferreus coegi plena est notitia ut huc
know five thousand members and and the
quinque milia autem et membris, et scitis
hard drive has the data on it right I
recta ferreus coegi quod habet in notitia sum
wonder if it's an employee even if it's
Mirum est etiam scriptor molestie
a lot don't worry
nolite ergo solliciti esse multus
and in a very exclusive club so if it
non solum plurima ac si natus
wasn't an employee it's got to be
non molestie ut suus 'got
somebody who's a member of the club and
quis socius sit et quis de clava
these are folks that are not probably in
hi sunt qui folks verisimile non est in
need of stealing a hard drive
ferreus coegi ex necessitate peccandum proclivior
I feel like they're implying that
Sentio amo ipsi erant 'quod involvat ubi dicitur,
encryption wasn't done like the hard
dura sicut factum Encryption
drive wasn't encrypted I'm not really
Im 'vere non est encrypted ne coegi
saying they did say that it was
dicens quod non esset dicere
password-protected but what that means I
-password tutis ut verum est quod ego
mean is it an Excel spreadsheet with a
cum sit an Praecedo spreadsheet est,
password on it that can easily be brute
ea bruti password facile
forced you know that's the thing that's
Quod ut 'res scis quia coactus est
not the last of this yeah right
non ultimum hoc ius yeah
all right the Pentagon's Defense
omne ius defensionis Pentagono est scriptor
Advanced Research Projects Agency or
Advanced Research Agency et Projects
DARPA is funding researchers who are
Inquisitores qui est sumptu DARPA
working on some kind of mind-control
quaedam animi opus in potestate,
chips that can be inserted into human
ut possit imponi in alterum eu hominum
brains to fix mood disorders the
modus in perturbationes cerebri figere
researchers from the University of
Inquisitores a Universitas
California at Massachusetts General
California Generalis apud Massachusetts
Hospital in Boston have reportedly begun
Hospitium habere parem in Boston inceperat
testing closed-loop brain implants these
temptationis clausis-cerebrum loop haec implantat
neural implants use artificial
neural uti artificialis inprïmïs ingeneratque inprïmïs
intelligence algorithms to detect
intelligentia est deprehendere algorithms
various mood disorders and to deliver
et libera mente variis perturbationes
electric shocks to jolt a person's brain
electrica offensionibusque parvis fragile in homine usque ad commovebo scriptor cerebrum
back into a healthy state the implants
operatur in statu sano
which generate electrical pulses to
quod generate electrica tremore pulsus,
control human feelings and behavior can
control hominum mores et affectus potest,
stimulate the brain to treat mental
incitare cerebrum est mentis tractare,
disorders including dementia and
et perturbationes inter deprehendi dementiam,
Alzheimer's experts also believe that
Etiam periti credere quod Alzheimer scriptor
the chips can be beneficial to patients
in eu aegris prodesse potest
with a whole range of health issues like
sicut cum tota sanitas exitibus
Parkinson's disease and chronic
Parkinson scriptor morbus chronicus est,
depression the chips have already been
iam enim in lacus eu
tested on six volunteers who have
Qui probatus sex consequat
epilepsy and have electrodes implanted
ut comitialis, ut electrodes insita
in their brain to help researchers track
inquisitores in cerebrum usque ad auxilium track
what is happening inside their brains
quod est fieri in medio cerebro
throughout the day as part of their
partem per diem
trial the researchers tracked the
iudicium autem inquisitores in idolum
volunteers brain activity and moods in
volones modi actionem in cerebro
detail over the course of one to three
decursu ad tres singillatim
weeks and eventually created an
et hebdomades eventually creata est
algorithm to decode these changing moods
hi variis modis algorithm decode
further analysis helped the researchers
Inquisitores ad ulterius analysis omnium decernente sententia
discover that delivering shocks to areas
offensionibusque parvis fragile sunt qui inveniunt delivering areas
of the brain that involved
quae cerebri implicari
decision-making and emotions can
decernendo potest animique affectionibus,
significantly improve the participants
participantium amplio significantly
performance in set tasks such as
set ut per perficiendi tasks
matching images of numbers or
numeri seu imagines matching
identifying emotions on faces the group
facies et coetus passiones identifying
is currently working with neuro
est currently operatus est neuro
ethicists to address the moral
ethica et moralis to address
implications of the project that's my
quod effectus huius coetus laboris mei
big concern right there
ius enim de magnis
is the moral ethics of the project I
moralis et ethicae de project est
mean I think it's cool if you can get a
puto, si te potest a frigus suus 'mean
little chip that you know potential
tu scis quod modicum chip potentiale
we could eradicate some of those things
elabi posset aliquod eorum
like epilepsy yeah I mean that'd be
ut comitialis, ut youd 'quod sit non yeah
amazing but I mean how quickly could you
sed quam cito poterat mirabile sit tibi
turn around and be like well we're just
ut bene nobis esset iustus et circum vertere
gonna implant this into our soldiers and
militibus nostris haec inserunt amet
suddenly you're controlling people what
quis continuit populus es repente
if you're doing it afterwards and
postea si discis
controlling some PTSD
proli quaedam PTSD
how is this going to play into marriages
Hoc est iens ut ludere conjugia inirent
look at my face look at my face do I
vultus meus faciem meam ad te faciam vultum meum ad vide
look happy no I'm not happy with every
Im 'laetus aspiciat Non est beatus, nullus ex omnibus
implant you get a free marriage
vos adepto a libero implantantur nuptias
certificate love the idea of this like
Quisque diligit similem ideam
to help against something like chronic
ad auxilium contra aliquid quasi inveterata
depression or a C or pure drug free
sive pura, sive tristitia, C medicamento libero
right drug free solution and what is the
et quod rectum est medicamento libero solution
brain but like the organ that is an
sed ut organum, quod est cerebrum
electrical impulse machine it makes
electrica impulsus apparatus facit
sense that too complex we don't
universa nobis sensum ut ne nimis
understand it you can't just open a
intelligunt quod non solum aperire
computer and say okay what's wrong with
bene dicere quid mali PC
this I'm gonna start short-circuiting
quod Im 'agnus dei-satus brevis circuiting
some of the electrical components see
video components de aliquo electrica
and some of it isn't like I'm thinking
et pars non est similis Cogito
something like depression right you know
quasi novi aliquid vobis rectum exanimationes incidamus
that's a serotonin level like that's not
ut planum est quod non serotonin
something that you can you know fix with
quid nosti quod vos can figere cum
a shock to the brain
inpulsa est in cerebrum
I mean well perhaps maybe it's not the
Bene maybe suus 'non intelliguntur forsitan me
serotonin that's the problem it's the
suus 'forsit per serotonin ut'
the like the reuptake errs like they
et similia similibus consistit reuptake
cause a depression drug is a serotonin
causa est locus cavus est medicamento, serotonin
reuptake inhibitor so the serotonin gets
serotonin reuptake precursor sic accipit
yes this is what it must feel like to
Sed hoc est simile sentiendum
hear me talk about computers it's true I
exaudi me loqui ut computers quod verum est
was listening to the radio on my way
est via mea a radio ad audiendum
into the studio today and and
et in Studio et hodie
interestingly enough there was a show on
Interestingly satis spectaculum fuit non ex
where people were in the audience we're
in quo sunt homines in auditorium sumus
asking questions and then they had
et interrogantem eos habuit
professionals in the industry answering
doctorum industria in Respondens
these questions it was really quite
hae quaestiones erat vere satis
entertaining and informative and one of
unum delectabiles nuntiisque
the questions was what is the cause of
quae causa fuit in quaestionum
chronic pain and how how does it exist
inveterata dolor et quam ut eam non est
if there is no injury right and the the
si iniuriae ius et
response from this professional from a
ex hac responsione professional
university I didn't catch their name or
universitates sive non capit suum nomen,
anything like that and didn't even
et quod usque non aliquid simile
intend to speak about it
animo loqui circa eam
said that it is actually the the neurons
dictum quod actualiter neurons
in the pain receptors and everything
in dolore omnia receptores,
else misfiring and and providing the
polest et alio modo ad alium: et misfiring
wrong information so you think that
notitia autem malum vobis videtur ut
there's pain and your brain says there's
illic 'et cerebrum dolor dicit illic'
pain and you feel the pain but the pain
dolorem sentire et dolorem et dolor in
doesn't exist and so they can't diagnose
et sic non possunt non est egritudo
it they can't fix it they can't you know
eo quod ipsi non possunt non figere scitis
what do you do how many Warrior amputee
quid agis quot Bellator amputee
--zz have that what's called phantom
qui est imago dicitur, quod suus '--zz
limb syndrome sure you know so I mean
crus syndrome sit certus ut nosti
there's a lot of potential good that can
illic 'multus of potential potest esse bonum,
come from this but again I go back to my
inde iterum redire ad aliud
first comment the moral implications I
Primus effectus sum moralis ineo
think this could go real bad real fast
Hanc rem malam rem posse ieiunare
if it's not reined in right which is why
Si non est rectum coquo
I'm happy they have some wasn't neuro
Im 'laetus habent aliquid non neuro
ethicists oh yeah that was good to see
O Yeah esset bonum, quod ethica videre
but yeah but like anything where where's
sed sane memini sed sicut quo aliquid est ibi
the line and who gets to control the
aciem regere invenientibus
technolon tier for this I would
Et si hoc versu impellunt, terno technolon
volunteer to have it done and here is
ut fiat hie Voluntarius
why because it said increased
propter quod dicitur augeri
performance in numbers and functions
in numeris et perficientur munera
could you imagine if finally after
potest imaginari si tandem post te
getting a chip implanted in my brain I
questus est insitum chip in cerebrum me
would understand the things that Robby
ut intelligeret Robby
said I don't think it works that way so
Non puto dictum est modo, quae operatur
helps you focus but take this to the
sed hoc adjuvat te, ad focus
next level I mean we already know all
Dico jam gradum noverim
the analytics that come from cell phones
cell phones et venire ut analytics
and your web usage imagine having that
et telam quam usus habens meditati
integrated with the chip that reads your
integrated chip cum vestris qui legit,
emotions that's it it reads emotions and
legit illud quod est passio est motus,
it under N it interprets yeah because
quod per N propter hoc interprets yeah
it's it's an AI I mean if it then goes
A. Dico si suus est deinde
Moo hey I can manipulate you from a
Heus te possum de EMUGIO manipulate
marketing standpoint and invoke these
invocat illa parte ipsum
emotions yeah with these I mean like I
memini me his adfectibus dico quasi
mean the sky's the limit with this
intelliguntur caelum est terminus huic
technology but man could it go bad and
Sed velit esse illud malum
and you think well they can't control
et bene cogitant, non possunt control
people's minds they can't put thoughts
mentium cogitationes non possunt
into your head and say you know but they
sed dico vobis quia et in capite tuo
could certainly walk you down the road
utique ambulatis in via
well here here's a suggestion do this or
hinc atque hinc vel hoc a suggestion
slow that or or beat up that guy you
vel hoc vel illo amari te pigeat verberatus
can't they can't do that it's not that
non possumus facere quod suus 'non ut
kind of mind control but have you ever
quaedam mentis potestate non habent umquam
been you know on your way to work you're
tu scis opus esse tuo ut vestri '
feeling pretty good and some idiot cuts
Sententia, pulchra et bona stultus secat
you off and all of a sudden there goes
exit et subito te
your day yeah you know or somebody you
aut quis vos scitis die yeah
know something happened
scitis quod factum est
somebody mistreats you when you're
Cum tu quis es male
checking out for your coffee or
vel capulus pro reprehendo sicco
something and and it can ruin your day
et dies tuus, et aliquid quo possis perdere,
and then it affects in turn your
et rursus tuus offendit
attitude and the way that you treat
et habitus ut vos tractare,
other people throughout that day and you
et alios in illa
know the shirt folks it's hard yeah it's
suus 'ferreus scire shirt folks suus' yeah
hard to regulate emotion in situations
difficile moderari motum in rebus
like that the facial recognition for
ut ne facialis recognitionem
moods would probably be great for people
modi esset verisimile esse populus quoniam magnus
who suffer from something like
quasi laborantes
Asperger's and where they have a really
Et ubi realiter non habent Asperger scriptor
hard time empathizing because they don't
Difficile empathizing quia non
easily read emotion on others anyway
Facile aliis in passione legitur usquam
thinking of getting a drone for
Cogitabat enim questus fucus
Christmas just a heads up you may need
Class aptent capitibus iustus opus est tibi
to qualify to fly in the UK under a new
fugere ad temperandum in in UK novum
legislation planned by the government
cogitavit leges ad regimen
drones weigh more than 250 grams could
ignavom fucos pecus plus valebit CCL of P. poterat
also be banned from flying near airports
Etiam aliquet nisl non interdictum volat prope
or above 2 or 400 feet in a crackdown on
seu CD super pedes sive per crackdown in II
unsafe flying police will also be given
dedit quoque volantes vigilum statio male fida
new powers to seize and ground drones
ignavom fucos pecus vires terram occuparent
which have been used in criminal
quae in criminalibus
activity the bill has been welcomed by
de actione legis receptus est
the pilots union which has warned of
admonuit autem unio, quae notare gubernatores
near misses involving drones and
ignavom fucos pecus et involving iuxta misses
aircraft saying that there have been
elit dixit quod ibi esse
eighty-one incidents that so far this
Haec una res in tantum octoginta
year up from 71 in 2016 and 29 in 2015
a LXXI anno usque MMXVI et in XXIX in MMXV
the union's general secretary Brian
unio est scriptor Brian Secretarius Generalis
struttin said these proposals are a sate
Haec dicit struttin autem sedebat
a step towards the safe integration of
integration per gradus ad tutum est
drones but until the new rules are in
ignavom fucos pecus donec nova praecepta, sed in
place the threat of a serious collision
locus est gravi comminatione ad occursum,
remains the proposed bill to be
qui manet quidem rogatione praescripta est
published in the spring would ensure
vere esset published in ensure
that owners of drones weighing more than
quod owners of appendens magis quam ignavum fucos pecus
250 grams would need to register and
CCL P. * I would postulo ut subcriptio et
take a test wow I wonder if that will be
Nescio, quia erit accipere temptare wow
like our written test or a flying test
nostra, sicut scriptum test test aut volantes
or that'd be cool yeah it's actually a
illa youd 'vel esse a frigus suus' vere yeah
race all right drones flying through a
ignavom fucos pecus a volitans recte genus
course or something like that no I think
aut sicut aliquid, quod utique non puto
it's it's literally just registration
suus 'suus' iustus ad verbum adnotatione
and and answering the test like a g1 or
, et test sicut et in solvendis aut g1
something it's time it's like a written
quod suus 'vicis suus' sicut scriptum
test yeah
test yeah
it's time for that for sure yeah the
certus ut suus 'tempus ad yeah
UK's Information Commissioner has huge
UK scriptor ingens est legatus Information
concerns about ubers data policies and
Ubers curam de notitia et Politiae
six following a breach that exposed the
quod patere ex his sex et contritionem
details of 57 million customers and
Details of LVII decies elit
drivers uber did not tell anyone about
ne cui dicerent de illo exactoribus uber did
the breach and actually paid a ransom to
super contritionem et quoque coluit, ut in quo ei propitier
hackers to delete the data Deputy
hackers ad delete notitia Deputy
Commissioner James Dibble Johnson said
James Johnson dixit LEGATUS Dibble
that these actions were unacceptable the
in his actionibus, ut sunt ingrata
ride-sharing company does have a
non equitare a turba, sharing
resource page for those who may be
Qui enim fieri potest resource page
affected Deputy Commissioner James
James litteras maiusculas minusculasque prorex LEGATUS
Dibble Johnson said the Information
Dibble Cicero dixit Information
Commissioner's Office would work with
Commissarium officium est hoc opus
the National Cyber Security Center to
in National Obses Center ut cyber
determine the scale of the breach and
determinet ordinem et sepium
how it affected people in the UK as well
ita affectus quoque hominibus quam in the UK
as considering the next steps that uber
proximus gradus est secundum quod inspicit rationes Uber
needed to take to comply with its data
ut cum suis notitia opus ad propinquos meos
protection obligations next year EU
EU officia tutelae deinde anno,
countries will radically alter data
funditus in terris data mutaverit iussionem
protection laws to offer consumers
offerre perussi legibus praesidio
greater control over the data that they
maior potestas est data est illi
share with companies Wow so uber not
communicet, ita societates Wow über
only kept the breach a secret but then
sed tunc non tenentur ad secretum ad contritionem
paid a hacker I guess today yeah when it
EGO coniecto yeah, cum hodie hoc solvit a Piratica
comes to uber I feel like they've just
Ive 'iustus sentio amo ipsi liber fit,
had about 12 months of complete
integrum erat circiter XII mensibus
butt-kicking Ayana
-blandeque coruscant kicking Ayana
I'm just screwing up front on various
Im 'iustus ante futuit sursum in variis
levels right every time they'd gone
Ius elit abiit, quotienscumque
ahead something went wrong and they my
praemisit aliquid abiit iniuriam, et non mihi
my feeling is they dealt with it
Ipsi vero superbe affectum meum est cum eo
not necessarily correctly and this is
Recte haec necessario
just another step in the case and it's
et alia iusta de causa ad gradum suus '
it's too bad if if you pay a hacker to I
si nimis est, si ego reddam in Piratica
guess if you pay a hacker then how do
deinde quomodo deberet si coniectare Piratica
you know how do they have proof that the
scis enim quomodo non est in probationem
hacker deleted the data that just to sir
Forum gratis data, quod justum est et deleta mi
you oh yeah I deleted that data that
O vos yeah, quae data est mihi delevit
actually leaked the story right now they
quaeque nunc ad fabulam actually
have the data and probably an ethical
et verisimile habere in notitia ethicam
hacker that they knew or had reference
et cum scirem Piratica ut referat
to do you think so
ut putatis quia inaniter ita
maybe they paid a ransom I did so that's
maybe sunt singuli pretium solvit sum ut suus '
not very talked about we talked about
non ipsum loquebatur circa nos loquebatur de
them
illis
no that was DJI I'm mixing up my stories
Im 'non miscentes meum DJI quae fabulas
yeah it makes me think about DJI story
yeah eum de me cogitare fabula DJI
last week and how a hacker was using the
Ultima septimana et ut esset a Piratica usura est
the bug
cimex
deprogrammed to show that her to you
ut ostenderet tibi deprogrammed eius
know submit a bug yes and had connected
Ita scire et cimex submittere coniunxerat
I wonder if it's a similar case to that
Nescio, suus 'a casu esse quod similis
oh that's true so in in this particular
O, quod verum est et in hoc maxime
case though I mean we got a look at the
etsi hoc casu, EGO got a vultus in medium
fact that this is what over a year ago
quod hoc per annum in ante
that this occurred so now the question
et nunc quod occurrit quaestio
comes up well why are we just hearing
Audiens autem bene quid iustus
about it now who leaked the information
Nunc quis de ea indicium leaked
I mean not every news news sources
Ut non sit omnibus nuntium nuntium sources
telling where the story came from but in
sed ubi vera ab historia
fact the this is that the CEO or not the
eo quod est vel non esse CEO
CEO but the head honcho anyways that it
CEO caput honcho, sed quod anyways
uber it was replaced maybe it was the
maybe hoc est pro uber est
CEO so that kept part of it and so he
Ut custodiri eum et ipse pars CEO
actually well first of all fired the the
bene quidem prima omnium est et accensus
folks that covered it up yes but also
Etiam sed sem operuit illum
then released a press release letting
Tunc dimisit sinit torcular release
people know that hey this has happened
qui sciunt, quod hoc factum est, heus
and it happened under not under my watch
et super custodiam meam ego non sub
but under the last guys why and you know
sed postremo cur tu guys
so that plays into it as well yeah so
memini ludos in tantum ut aeque
he's trying to clean up I think which is
puto hes 'trying ad mundare usque quae est
good mm-hmm
hmm mm bonum,
it's a great service so I hope that they
quod suus magna ut spero
get it together and they're able to
et tu adepto simul poterit
that's the thing is I mean they do offer
dico quod res offerunt
good service it just it's like man some
sicut quod bona opera hominis aliqua suus 'similis
bad calls have been made speaking of a
factum est loqui de vocat mala sunt
good service Skype call and messaging
Cras et bene vocat Nuntius
service has been removed from app stores
servitium remotus est a app stores
in China including the Apple App Store
in Sina inter quas Apple App Store
Apple says it's one of several apps to
Dicit ei unus ex pluribus apps ut Apple scriptor
have been removed after the government
sunt, postquam remota imperium
said it does not comply with local law
dixit ad propinquos meos non locali lege
Skype owner Microsoft told the BBC the
Microsoft nuntiavit BBC in circo dominus
app had been temporarily removed and the
et remotum erat tempus app
company was working to reinstate the app
turba opus erat, ut iterato app
as soon as possible the app is also no
et non quam primum hoc enim app
longer available for download on Andrew
iam quae tractari possunt ex Andrew
Android app stores in China media
Android app in Sina media stores
reports suggested disruptions of Skype
suggesserant tradit disruptions Skype
started in October Apple said in a
Lacus in in October ait coepi
statement we have been notified by the
dicitur enim sunt per certiorem
Ministry of Public Security that a
Publica, quae Ministerio et Security
number of voice over Internet Protocol
vox in multis Internet Protocol
apps do not comply with local law
apps ad propinquos meos et non locali lege
therefore these apps have been removed
ideo remota Apps
from the App Store in China
de app in Sina
Skype when downloaded from outside
Cum extra downloaded from skype
China's firewall has been seen as a semi
Sinis scriptor firewall visa est sicut semi
secure way of discussing sensitive
securam viam discussing sensitivo
topics away from the eyes and ears of
locis ab oculis auribusque
China's State Security Skype is just the
Sinis scriptor publica Securitatis Skype est iustus
latest in a string of foreign owned
tardus per filum de aliena substantia
digital and Internet platforms including
and Internet inter digital platforms
alphabets Google Facebook and Twitter
Twitter Facebook et Google alphabetis
which are unavailable to Chinese users
sunt unavailable ut Chinese quod users
Wow what do they do in China if they
Wow si quid isti faciunt in Sina
don't have like Twitter and Facebook
Non sicut Facebook et Twitter
they have their own stuff yeah that's
Yeah quod materia propria
right yeah and it's government monitored
yeah suus 'ius et imperium monitored
and government controlled regulated and
sobrie, et regimen instituta et
do you think that it'll ever be a lot I
ut youll 'umquam fore putatis quia inaniter multum me
guess maybe if Skype allows it to be
Cras id concedit quod maybe si coniecto
monitored yeah that would be the thing
Yeah viverra res esset
if Skype were to put servers in China
Cras, si essent in Sina posuit servers
and make them monitor a bull by the
ut monitor eos ab agresti tauro,
government then but see the way the way
quomodo tunc videre, sed modo imperium
things work though is when there's an
Etsi illic 'opus est res, ubi est
app that works well somebody in China
quis tam app qui operatur in Sina
comes up with their own version of it
ex eo venit cum suis poema
right I see it all the time so it's only
sic suus 'tempore videre ius illud solum
gonna be a matter of time before they
materia prius tempore sit amet
have their own version of Skype which
Cras quæ sua sunt versionem
will then have integration with regular
tunc integrationem regulari
Skype but because they'll they'll be
Cras sed Venerem non ero
there back they won't be allowed to do
tergum est quod non liceat facere
integration they won't be able to tap
integration se non posse ICTUS
into calling to Skype because that's the
Cras vocant, ut, quod in eo est
whole thing that's about regulating
totum quod est de regula
although as you say if it was if it was
Quanquam si dicas si
a regulated app that was connected to
quae coniuncta regulatus app
sky then that app could be yes could it
Sic ergo potuit esse caelum app
could I can't see that's such a hard
Non possum videre potest quod tam difficile
thing could you imagine being a software
non posset imaginari aliquid esse a software
developer and releasing something like
et aliquid quasi elit releasing
Skype maintaining its servers
Circo semper conservet naturam indolemque servers
maintaining the service making it so
qui custodis officium facis ergo eam
that I can call China for free and then
voca me gratis et Sina
having them to shut it down yeah there's
Gaudete et illic haberet claudere
potentially billion plus customers right
customers billion plus juris in potentia;
now I cannot imagine Wow
Et nunc non possumus imaginari Wow
China's a big country you want to be
Sinis est a magnus regionem vis
able to market to them sure have
certe non posse fori facilitatem ad eos
services accessible so maybe Skype will
ita maybe Cras faciet officia accessible
come up with a way of making it far more
sed longe aliter ascendere faciens
accessible and then be allowed to
et licere accessible
reintegrate I think about all the like
Ego similis fere omni reintegrate
foreign exchange students and everything
aliena commutationem alumni et omnia
and you know that's how we communicate
et scis quam communicamus
back with
reversus est
if you know parents and it's family
sed nosti genus parentum
members and stuff so that's certainly be
et suus 'certe potest membris, ut supellectilem
tough upon them and use like I know with
et cum eis utuntur quasi lenta Scio
some of the online games that I play you
tecum ludere online ludos ut aliquid ex
know we keep connected outside with an
Nescio an mandata quae extrinsecus
app called discord and it's got the
cum discordiae, et vocavit app 'got
right shot - that'll be blocked if it
ius iaculat - cipiendis inhio, quod youll 'si
isn't already well there's lots of users
non iam tum illic 'lots of users
from China yeah yeah I mean you've got
yeah non intelliguntur a te surrexit Sinis yeah
kale which is also a Chinese chatting
et Sinica est, olus quam fabulamur
app I believe they've just added video
Credo quod video app nuper additae
integration you know so I mean there's
integration scitis ut illic 'mean
lots of other ways around it it's no
lots of vias alio circa id quod suus 'non
different than like whatsapp or whatever
quidquid aliud huiusmodi whatsapp
so yeah there are the ways but yeah for
yeah sic sunt in via, sed quia yeah
now
nunc
big thanks to Roy W Nash in our
John magnas gratias W Nash nostri
community of viewers for submitting
conventu et pro exhibenda viewers
stories test this week thanks for
tibi gratias ago pro fabulis tuum probandi hoc septimana
watching the category-five TV newsroom
Genus quinque-vigilantes TV newsroom
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
Similis est, et nolite oblivisci subscribe
all your attack news there's a slight
Evangelium omni impetu exiguo illic
Linux bias and for more free content to
Et magis liberum contentus ad pondus Linux
be sure to check out our website from
ex certa Lorem website
the category-five TV newsroom and sasha
genus, et quinque TV newsroom Sasha
Rickman
Rickman
[Music]
[Musica]
[Applause]
[Plausus]